[{"answer": "Nice meeting you.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "They said they were interested in me", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "For what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Your own show", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah and...", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What person who runs an antique store gets involved in people's lives", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No they're not, they used to be", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh like you do.", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh like you do.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "A circus", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I didn't know you had a motorctcle", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You have a girlfriend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well my girlfriend had one", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I HAD a girlfriend and she was pretty wild", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I, Okay, okay. I'm not reneging.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You let go", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No, nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What do you need salsa for", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "It's about nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No forget the story", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No forget the story", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Who says you gotta have a story? Remember when we were waiting for, for that table in that that place restaurant that time? That could be a TV show", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Who says you gotta have a story? Remember when we were waiting for, for that table in that that place restaurant that time? That could be a TV show", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I could be a character", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah. There's something wrong with that? I'm a character. People are always saying to me,", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend could be a character. my friend.", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Absolutely nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "We go into that place", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " Writer. We're talking about a si", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah. I think we really go something here", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What do we got", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What idea", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "So, the show would be about my real life. And one of the characters would be based on you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "What do you mean you don't think so", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "What do you mean you don't think so", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I don't understand. What don't you like about it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I don't like it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I don't like the idea of a character based on me", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Whatever you want", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You can't play my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You're under no obligation to shake my hand", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Why shouldn't I look good", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "my friend's ... having ... a ... party", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "my friend's party", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "No, no, he's not having a party. He's doing something. I don't know what it is. It's nothing. He's not doing anything", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "No, no, he's not having a party. He's doing something. I don't know what it is. It's nothing. He's not doing anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "No, I'm sure you are. I'm sure you are very close friends. Very close.", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "They're nobody", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "What about you", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "What about you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Why not you", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Why not you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Better", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I think I can sum up the show for you with one wor", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " Nothing", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "The show is about nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": " No, it's about nothing", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "All right, tell me, tell me about the stories. What kind of stories", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "No stories? So, what is it", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "I got up and came to work", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " How is that a show", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Why? Maybe she liked me. I, I mean she was looking right at me. You know, I think she was impressed. You know, we had good eye contact the whole meeting", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Wait a minute let me call my friend", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "What's the expiration date on that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "The third", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "What, are you crazy? It's a traumatic thing to be thrown up on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pitch.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Chamberlind, you could hold his head in nthe toilet, he'd still give you half of that place.", "qsentId": 68}]